webpackJsonp([65856866535745],{69:function(e,a){},467:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function r(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e:{default:e}}function i(e,a){if(!(e instanceof a))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}function o(e,a){if(!e)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return!a||"object"!=typeof a&&"function"!=typeof a?e:a}function n(e,a){if("function"!=typeof a&&null!==a)throw new TypeError("Super expression must either be null or a function, not "+typeof a);e.prototype=Object.create(a&&a.prototype,{constructor:{value:e,enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0}}),a&&(Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e,a):e.__proto__=a)}a.__esModule=!0;var l=t(1),c=r(l),s=t(44);r(s);t(69);var u=[{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-1",href:"#collapse-1",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-2",href:"#collapse-2",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-3",href:"#collapse-3",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-4",href:"#collapse-4",display:!0}],d=[{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-5",href:"#collapse-5",display:!0},{question:"Who owns Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-6",href:"#collapse-6",display:!0},{question:"Why am I having trouble logging in?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-7",href:"#collapse-7",display:!0},{question:"How can I contact Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-8",href:"#collapse-8",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-9",href:"#collapse-9",display:!0},{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-10",href:"#collapse-10",display:!0}],f=function(e){var a=e.question,t=e.answer,r=e.id,i=e.href;return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"mb-4"},c.default.createElement("h5",null,c.default.createElement("i",{className:"fas fa-caret-right"}),c.default.createElement("a",{className:"text-dark","data-toggle":"collapse",href:i,"aria-expanded":"false","aria-controls":r},a)),c.default.createElement("p",{className:"collapse m-3 p-0 mr-5",id:r},t))},m=function(e){function a(){return i(this,a),o(this,e.apply(this,arguments))}return n(a,e),a.prototype.render=function(){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"pt-5 pb-5 mb-2",id:"content-14"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container pt-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"row"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-8 col-md-10 col-sm-12 mx-auto"},c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"profile-title display-4 mb-2 font-weight-normal"},"Questions"),c.default.createElement("p",{className:"lead"},"Frequently asked questions"),c.default.createElement("br",null),c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2"},"Product"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),u.filter(function(e){return e.display===!0}).map(function(e){return c.default.createElement(f,e)}),c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2 mt-5"},"Sales"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),d.filter(function(e){return e.display===!0}).map(function(e){return c.default.createElement(f,e)})))))},a}(l.Component);a.default=m,e.exports=a.default}});
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-fa-q-js-466226a3c170f73dbbc5.js.map